<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dart Games</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="cricket_rules">The aim is to \'close\' these numbers on the board, and get the highest point score. The player/team to do so first, wins. Each player/team takes turns throwing three darts in a row (an \'inning\'). To close an inning, the player/team needs to score three of a number – with three singles, a single and a double, or a triple. Once a player/team scores three of a number, they ‘own’ it. Once a player/team closes an inning, he/they may score points on that number until the opponent also closes that inning. All numerical scores are added together. Once both players/teams have scored three of a number, it’s \'closed\', and it can’t be scored on by either player/team. To close the bullseye, the outer bull counts as a single, and the inner bull counts as a double. Numbers can be \'owned\' or \'closed\' in any order. No need to call your shot. The player/team that closes all the innings first and has the most points, wins. If both sides are tied on points, the first player/team to close all innings is the winner. If a player/team closes all innings first, but is behind on points, they need to keep scoring on any innings that aren’t closed until they make up the points or their opponent wins the game.</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="score_increase">Score Increase</string>
    <string name="RTW_rules">The object is to be the first player to hit every number on the board in sequence from 1-20. Hitting any part of the number – single, double or triple – counts, and numbers must be hit in order to advance to the next. Players alternate after three throws. The first player to hit a 20 is the winner.</string>
    <string name="tv_301">301</string>
    <string name="rules_301">Each player/team starts with 301 points. The goal is to reach zero, exactly, by subtracting the amount you score in a turn from the number you have left. Before you start subtracting though, each player/team has to ‘double in’ (hit any one of 21 possible doubles including the double bull). To end the game, players also need to double out (eg. if you’re on 28, you’ll need to throw a double 14 to reach zero, and if you hit a single 14, your next target is a double 7). Hitting more pints than you have left to get to zero will get you ‘busted’ (this is not what you want). That means the turn is over and next time it’s your turn you’ll start again from your previous score.</string>
</resources>